<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sessions on Josh Wood</title>
    <link>https://joshix.com/tags/sessions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sessions on Josh Wood</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>j@joshix.com (Josh Wood)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>j@joshix.com (Josh Wood)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 Josh Wood.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 22:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://joshix.com/tags/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Courtyard</title>
      <link>https://joshix.com/2006/10/13/courtyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>j@joshix.com (Josh Wood)</author>
      <guid>https://joshix.com/2006/10/13/courtyard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Paros. October 2006.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stood on the rail and looked over the stone wall of the courtyard&lt;br /&gt;
Through the crosshairs of the crucifix atop the blue dome of the church&lt;br /&gt;
I saw people moving in the house-lights on the hillside&lt;br /&gt;
They seemed like signals&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roy Orbison</title>
      <link>https://joshix.com/2005/12/07/roy-orbison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2005 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>j@joshix.com (Josh Wood)</author>
      <guid>https://joshix.com/2005/12/07/roy-orbison/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;pretty woman, give your smile to me&lt;br /&gt;
that is an imperative&lt;br /&gt;
I want to try it on&lt;br /&gt;
and I promise&lt;br /&gt;
not to wipe it off&lt;br /&gt;
with my greaserag this time&lt;br /&gt;
that last incident having been merely&lt;br /&gt;
a confusion of identity of me&lt;br /&gt;
for my brother who is not me&lt;br /&gt;
but is often mistaken for me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;he’s the one who can play guitar&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An advantage of angles</title>
      <link>https://joshix.com/2005/11/15/an-advantage-of-angles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2005 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>j@joshix.com (Josh Wood)</author>
      <guid>https://joshix.com/2005/11/15/an-advantage-of-angles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kansas City/Paros. November 2005.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not every night is different&lt;br /&gt;
most begin with much the same choreography&lt;br /&gt;
a geometry of sky folding closed and Sound&lt;br /&gt;
thrown out of a day’s dance with the wind&lt;br /&gt;
when Silence cuts in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stars pick out jasmine’s shadow negative against&lt;br /&gt;
their black matting, their paper backing, where&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tonight it seems Orion aims his dart on a course&lt;br /&gt;
straight through the red heart of Mars and into&lt;br /&gt;
the moon’s sickly face for a trick shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As that pierced moon you have moved through&lt;br /&gt;
vast darkrooms bigger than this ocean-mirror sky&lt;br /&gt;
carrying photographs to be finished&lt;br /&gt;
on the process you invented in the bath one night&lt;br /&gt;
that the Kodak folks finally shook you down for. Tonight’s&lt;br /&gt;
moon would not brighten these gaping vault closets with&lt;br /&gt;
futile red lights and no poster on the bulwark walls&lt;br /&gt;
of this shadowbox could reduce the dimensions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rooms too big and black for living or falling asleep in,&lt;br /&gt;
walls too high for leaping, but you have a chance&lt;br /&gt;
to throw your hat over and you see that&lt;br /&gt;
the guests walk with the stiff steps of the uninvited&lt;br /&gt;
before you realize you arrived right on time&lt;br /&gt;
fit the dress code on the placard to a tee&lt;br /&gt;
but when trying to leave looked for nickels or dimes lost&lt;br /&gt;
in the funnel to the sewer line beneath the carpet&lt;br /&gt;
laid by man for dogs and nuns treading separately&lt;br /&gt;
past the case that locks the dirty negatives and&lt;br /&gt;
the chemicals. (You should not breathe these.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You thought your lab partner stood near the other end’s exit&lt;br /&gt;
to pull on the string with the clothespins and things&lt;br /&gt;
that aren’t pictures yet hanging. “Why won’t you pull&lt;br /&gt;
the line away from me? I can’t push it.&lt;br /&gt;
Are you reeling now?&lt;br /&gt;
Can you hear me? Is it so dark that you’re deaf?&lt;br /&gt;
If so you won’t have noticed the noise that hides you.&lt;br /&gt;
Or are you raiding some other pantry?” (that will be&lt;br /&gt;
such broad blackness just like this one&lt;br /&gt;
with all the same mundane dunking, dousing,&lt;br /&gt;
pressing, printing, hanging, cutting machines.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The door you must find by feeling and no&lt;br /&gt;
lightswitch sits near the jamb it’s in&lt;br /&gt;
But finally you get out as you got in, but thinking&lt;br /&gt;
as you push your head through the exit that&lt;br /&gt;
These marbles are plaster made forgetful&lt;br /&gt;
massaged with chisels until depicting&lt;br /&gt;
just the one thing but with the advantage of angles&lt;br /&gt;
in the light tonight’s moon shines they define subtlety.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inked (Don’t You Call Me (two (too) Haikus))</title>
      <link>https://joshix.com/2005/11/13/inked/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2005 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>j@joshix.com (Josh Wood)</author>
      <guid>https://joshix.com/2005/11/13/inked/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kansas City. November 2005.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;triple ribbon is&lt;br /&gt;
efficient because it&lt;br /&gt;
abandoned hue&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;any color you&lt;br /&gt;
want so long as it is black&lt;br /&gt;
like Henry Ford said&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>